Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG 42.5
New York University Archives
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-198
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Shipping, Returns and Other Miscellaneous, 1988 May-1995 March (Box II:8, Folder 27)
    - Eric Avery -- Works on Paper (Small Gallery), 1988 April-July (Box II:8, Folder 28)
    - Twelve From New York -- The 1988 Selections From the Nordstern Collection, 1987 November-1988 October (Box II:8, Folder 29)
    - Show and Tell -- Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box II:8, Folder 30)
    - Show and Tell -- Budget, 1985 (Box II:8, Folder 31)
    - Show and Tell -- Financial and Other Miscellaneous, 1986 December (Box II:8, Folder 32)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders List, 1988 September-October (Box II:8, Folder 33)
    - Show and Tell -- Institution Lenders (A-G), 1987 October-1989 January (Box II:8, Folder 34)
    - Show and Tell -- Institution Lenders (N-Z), 1987 October-1988 November (Box II:8, Folder 35)
    - Show and Tell -- Private Lenders, 1987 October-1988 November (Box II:8, Folder 36)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders, 1987 November-1988 November (Box II:8, Folder 37)
    - Show and Tell -- Loan Rejections/Dropped, 1987 October-1988 March (Box II:8, Folder 38)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders and Other Miscellaneous, 1987 October-1988 November (Box II:8, Folder 39)
    - Show and Tell -- Loans and Shipping, 1988 June-November (Box II:8, Folder 40)
    - Show and Tell -- Shipping (Pick Up), 1988 July-October (Box II:8, Folder 41)
    - Landmarks of NY -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Show and Tell) (Box II:8, Folder 42)
    - Landmarks of NY -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Show and Tell), 1988 August-September (Box II:8, Folder 43)
    - Luc Courchesue -- Encyclopedia Chiaroscuro, 1985-1988 (Box II:8, Folder 44)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Correspondence, 1986 January-1989 February (Box II:8, Folder 45)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Contract, 1988 May 23 (Box II:8, Folder 46)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Shipping, 1988 October-1989 May (Box II:8, Folder 47)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Invoices, 1988 October-November (Box II:8, Folder 48)
    - Shelly Bachman -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Wolfli), 1988 October-1989 January (Box II:8, Folder 49)
    - Michael Landy, 1989 January-October (Box II:8, Folder 50)
    - French Revolution -- Proposed Exhibits (1 of 2), 1985-1988 (Box II:8, Folder 51)
    - French Revolution -- Proposed Exhibits (2 of 2), 1987 (Box II:8, Folder 52)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Correspondence, 1987 September-1989 March (Box II:8, Folder 53)
    - Politics and Polemics -- February 11 Dinner, 1989 February (Box II:8, Folder 54)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Contract, 1988 September-November (Box II:8, Folder 55)
    - Poletics and Polemics -- Shipping, 1988 September-1989 June (Box II:8, Folder 56)
    - Politics and Polemics -- NEH Proposal, 1987 (Box II:8, Folder 57)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Materials, 1985 June-1988 May (Box II:9, Folder 1)
    - Masami Teraoka -- Small Gallery, 1988 January-1989 April (Box II:9, Folder 2)
    - Masami Teraoka -- Small Gallery, 1988 January-1989 January (Box II:9, Folder 3)
    - Andy Warhol -- Correspondence, 1986 May-1990 August (Box II:9, Folder 4)
    - Andy Warhol -- NEH Proposal and Donna De Salvo Resume, 1986-1988 (Box II:9, Folder 5)
    - Andy Warhol -- Press Photos, Returns, Requests, 1989 January-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 6)
    - Andy Warhol -- Studio Museum/Pedestal, 1989 March-May (Box II:9, Folder 7)
    - Andy Warhol -- Guest List, 1989 February (Box II:9, Folder 8)
    - Andy Warhol -- Donna De Salvo Contract, 1988 February 3 (Box II:9, Folder 9)
    - Andy Warhol -- General Travel File, 1989 September-November (Box II:9, Folder 10)
    - Andy Warhol -- Shipping/Ollendorff (1st Tour: Carnegie, Serpentine, ICA), Circa 1989-1990 (Box II:9, Folder 11)
    - Andy Warhol -- Dispersal (1 of 2), 1990 April-1991 January (Box II:9, Folder 12)
    - Andy Warhol -- Dispersal (2 of 2), 1990 October (Box II:9, Folder 13)
    - Andy Warhol -- Tour (ICA, Carnegie, Serpentine), 1989 April-July (Box II:9, Folder 14)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (ICA, Philadelphia), 1989 April-1990 January (Box II:9, Folder 15)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Carnegie Museum of Art), 1988 December-1989 November (Box II:9, Folder 16)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Serpentine Gallery), 1989 January-1990 March (Box II:9, Folder 17)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Foundation Cartier), 1989 December-1995 July (Box II:9, Folder 18)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Newport Harbor Art Museum), 1989 September-1990 March (Box II:9, Folder 19)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Lingotto, Turin), 1989 November-1990 October (Box II:9, Folder 20)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Shipping/Extended Tour to Newport ,Turin, Versailles), 1989 December-1990 October (Box II:9, Folder 21)
    - Andy Warhol - Shipping ,Pickup and Returns of Objects Not Touring (February 1989), 1989 January-May (Box II:9, Folder 22)
    - Andy Warhol -- Works Not Traveling to Newport, Lingotte, Cartier, 1989 November-December (Box II:9, Folder 23)
    - Andy Warhol -- Works Not Traveling to Carnegie, Serpentine, ICA, 1988 December-1989 (Box II:9, Folder 24)
    - Andy Warhol -- Extended Loan List, Undated (Box II:9, Folder 25)
    - Andy Warhol -- Loans(Rejections/Dropped), 1988 June-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 26)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lender Lists, Undated (Box II:9, Folder 27)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (John Ardoin), 1988 July-1992 February (Box II:9, Folder 28)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Alison Beyea), 1988 October-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 29)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Simeon Braguin), 1988 January-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 30)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Stephen Bruce), 1988 November-1989 July (Box II:9, Folder 31)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Bruttal/Warhol Foundation), 1989 January-1990 July (Box II:9, Folder 32)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (John Butler), 1988 October-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 33)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Johnston and Carnegie), 1988 July-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 34)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Alvin Chereskin), 1988 December-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 35)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Inman Cook), 1988 June-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 36)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Rainer Crone), 1989 April-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 37)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Anthony D'Offay Gallery, London), 1989 February-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 38)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Betty Lou Davis), 1988 December-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 39)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mr. and Mrs. Arthur Edelman), 1988 December-1990 July (Box II:9, Folder 40)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Findley-F.I.T.), 1989 March-May (Box II:9, Folder 41)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Gene Federico), 1988 December-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 42)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mr. and Mrs. Ronald Feldman), 1988 December-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 43)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Otto Fenn), 1988 December-1990 July (Box II:9, Folder 44)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Steve Frankfurt), 1989 July-1990 July (Box II:9, Folder 45)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Suzie Frankfurt), 1988 December-1989 May (Box II:9, Folder 46)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Tina Fredericks), 1988 June-1990 July (Box II:9, Folder 47)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Amy Gassner-Starks), 1988 December-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 48)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Jacqueline Gonnet), 1988 December-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 49)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mr. and Mrs. Guillermo De Osma), 1988 August-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 50)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Alison B. Harwood), 1988 December-1989 June (Box II:9, Folder 51)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Richard Holmes), 1988 September-1991 January (Box II:9, Folder 52)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Art Kane), 1988 December-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 53)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Leonard Kessler), 1988 December-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 54)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (George Klauber), 1988 December-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 55)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Tom Lacy), 1988 December-1992 June (Box II:9, Folder 56)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Kenneth J. Lane), 1988 December-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 57)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Kate Lloyd), 1989 February-1990 March (Box II:9, Folder 58)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Christian Marclay), 1988 August-1991 January (Box II:9, Folder 59)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Keith McCarthy), 1988 December-1991 January (Box II:9, Folder 60)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Hopps/Menil Collection), 1989 January-December (Box II:9, Folder 61)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Druesedow/Metropolitan Museum), 1989 January-May (Box II:9, Folder 62)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Melissa Meyer), 1989 January-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 63)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Fritzie Miller), 1988 May-1989 May (Box II:9, Folder 64)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Robert Miller Gallery), 1989 March-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 65)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Barbara Moore), 1988 December-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 66)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Gene Moore), 1989 February-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 67)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mr. and Mrs. Robert Pliskin), 1988 August-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 68)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Radio Advertising Bureau), 1988 August-1991 January (Box II:9, Folder 69)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Buddy Radisch), 1988 December-1989 May (Box II:9, Folder 70)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Luigiano Rossi), 1988 December-1989 November (Box II:9, Folder 71)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mala Rubenstein), 1988 December-1990 July (Box II:9, Folder 72)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Douglas Sackfield), 1989 January-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 73)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Schultz/Bert Greene Estate), 1988 June-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 74)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Babs Simpson), 1989 February-December (Box II:9, Folder 75)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Frank Streich), 1988 December-1991 February (Box II:9, Folder 76)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Tiffany and Co.), 1988 December-1989 December (Box II:9, Folder 77)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (James Warhola), 1988 August-1990 December (Box II:9, Folder 78)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Yale University Art Gallery), 1989 January-October (Box II:9, Folder 79)
    - Andy Warhol -- Insurance Reports, 1989 (Box II:9, Folder 80)
    - Zuka -- The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery), 1986 November-1989 February (Box II:9, Folder 81)
    - Mike Bidlo (Window Installation in Conj. with Warhol Exhibit), 1989 February-September (Box II:9, Folder 82)
    - Mike Bidlo (Window Installation in Conj. with Warhol Exhibition), 1989 March-September (Box II:9, Folder 83)
    - Robert Morris -- NEH Proposal, Circa 1986-1988 (Box II:10, Folder 1)
    - Robert Morris -- Correspondence, 1986 July-1989 July (Box II:10, Folder 2)
    - Robert Morris -- Dinner (5/22), 1989 (Box II:10, Folder 3)
    - Robert Morris -- Loans and Lender Lists, CIrca 1987-1989 (Box II:10, Folder 4)
    - Robert morris -- Lenders, 1988 June-1989 October (Box II:10, Folder 5)
    - Robert Morris -- Shipping, 1988 May-1989 August (Box II:10, Folder 6)
    - Bernard Frize -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Robert Morris), 1989 May-July (Box II:10, Folder 7)
    - Weegee -- NEH Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box II:10, Folder 8)
    - Ching Ho Cheng -- Invitation List, Circa 1989 (Box II:10, Folder 10)
    - Ching Ho Cheng -- Lenders, 1989 August-1990 January (Box II:10, Folder 11)
    - Excommunication -- Correspondence, 1989 August-November (Box II:10, Folder 12)
    - Weegee -- Photographs/Framing, 1989 June-July (Box II:10, Folder 9)
    - Excommunication -- Rick Bolton, 1989 October-1990 February (Box II:10, Folder 13)
    - Excommunication -- Steve Evans, 1989 October-1990 January (Box II:10, Folder 14)
    - Excommunication -- The Jewish Museum, 1989 October-1990 January (Box II:10, Folder 15)
    - Excommunication -- Hillary Leone, 1989 October-1990 January (Box II:10, Folder 16)
    - Excommunication -- Anthony Reynolds Gallery, 1989 October-1990 January (Box II:10, Folder 17)
    - Excommunication -- Anthony Reynolds Gallery, 1989-1990 September (Box II:10, Folder 18)
    - Excommunication -- Bernice Steinbaum Gallery, 1989 November-1990 January (Box II:10, Folder 19)
    - Excommunication -- Mizra Tabrizian, 1989 September-1990 January (Box II:10, Folder 20)
    - Excommunication -- Shipping, 1989 October-1991 February (Box II:10, Folder 21)
    - Hujar -- Fundraising, Correspondence Lists and Other Miscellaneous, 1989 February-1991 June (Box II:10, Folder 22)
    - Hujar -- Lenders, 1989 December-1991 February (Box II:10, Folder 23)
    - Hujar -- Traveling Exhibition, 1990 June-1991 April (Box II:10, Folder 24)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Correspondence, 1989 September-1990 June (Box II:10, Folder 25)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Lannan Foundation Grant Application, 1987-1988 (Box II:10, Folder 26)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Conservation Treatment (1 of 2), 1990 (Box II:10, Folder 27)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Conservation Treatment (2 of 2), 1990 (Box II:10, Folder 28)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Shipping, 1990 February-May (Box II:10, Folder 29)
    - Gerhard Richter -- The Saint Louis Art Museum Exhibition Contract, 1990 February (Box II:10, Folder 30)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Symposium, 1990 February-May (Box II:10, Folder 31)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Correspondence, 1989 July-1990 March (Box II:10, Folder 32)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Graeme Murray Gallary/John Weber, Fidlay, Goldsworthy, Cooper, 1990 January-September (Box II:10, Folder 33)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Helen Chadwick), 1990 April (Box II:10, Folder 34)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Graeme Murray Gallery/John Weber, Findlay, Goldsworthy, Cooper), 1990 April-September (Box II:10, Folder 35)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Lisson Gallery/John Virtue, Karshad), 1990 April-September (Box II:10, Folder 36)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Louver Gallery NY/John Virtue, L.A. Louver), 1990 March-May (Box II:10, Folder 37)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Joe McCrindle), 1990 April-July (Box II:10, Folder 38)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Richard Upton), 1990 March-June (Box II:10, Folder 39)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Landscape at the End of the Century (Shipping), 1990 March-1991 February (Box II:10, Folder 40)
    - Peter Sebok -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Paysage Demoralise), 1990 April-July (Box II:10, Folder 41)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum Correspondence, 1987 December-1988 July (Box II:10, Folder 42)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Contemporary Art Museum, Houston Correspondence, 1988 August-1989 June (Box II:10, Folder 43)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- General Correspondence, 1986 May-1991 April (Box II:10, Folder 44)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Institute of Contemporary Art, Nagoya Correspondence (1 of 2), 1987 December-1990 November (Box II:10, Folder 45)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Institute of Contemporary Art, Nagoya Correspondence (2 of 2), 1988 May-1991 May (Box II:10, Folder 46)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- ICA, Tokyo General Correspondence, 1988 May-1990 May (Box II:10, Folder 47)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- ISE Correspondence, 1987 July-1988 March (Box II:10, Folder 48)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Japan Foundation Correspondence, 1983 September-1991 March (Box II:10, Folder 49)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Japan-U.S. Friendship Correspondence, 1987 July-1988 March (Box II:10, Folder 50)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- MIT Correspondence, 1986 November-1991 February (Box II:10, Folder 51)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Nanjo Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box II:10, Folder 52)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- National Museum of Art, Osaka Correspondence, 1987 February-1990 October (Box II:10, Folder 53)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Other Possible Venues Correspondence, 1987 December-1988 October (Box II:10, Folder 54)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- San Francisco MOMA Correspondence, 1987 December-1989 June (Box II:10, Folder 55)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Seattle Art Museum Correspondence, 1988 March-1990 October (Box II:10, Folder 56)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Tomiaki Yamamoto Correspondence, 1986 September-1987 September (Box II:10, Folder 57)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Asian Cultural Council Correspondence, 1987 March-December (Box II:10, Folder 58)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- San Francisco MOMA 6/14-8/6, 1989 and AT&T Grant, 1989 March-1990 August (Box II:10, Folder 59)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum, 1989 July-October (Box II:10, Folder 60)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- MIT, Boston, 1989 October-1990 June (Box II:10, Folder 61)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Seattle Art Museum, 1989 Septmber-1990 April (Box II:10, Folder 62)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati, 1989 October-1990 August (Box II:10, Folder 63)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Contemporary Art Museum, Houston, 1989 October-1990 November (Box II:10, Folder 64)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Conservation, 1989 June-1990 November (Box II:10, Folder 65)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- ICA, Tokyo Restoration, 1989 January-1990 December (Box II:10, Folder 66)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Contracts, 1987 July-1989 June (Box II:10, Folder 67)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- MIT Contracts, 1988 June-September (Box II:10, Folder 68)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Publishing Agreement, 1992 June-November (Box II:10, Folder 69)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Grants, 1988 January-1989 February (Box II:10, Folder 70)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Thomas Sokolowski's Trips, 1988 May-1989 July (Box II:10, Folder 71)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Travel Expenses, 1989 Augsut-December (Box II:10, Folder 72)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Book Orders Sent to MIT, 1989 January-July (Box II:10, Folder 73)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Restaurants, Beer, etc for Opening and Invitation Lists, 1990 August (Box II:10, Folder 74)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Shipping, 1989 May-August (Box II:10, Folder 75)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Grey Gallery Shipping, 1990 August-1994 November (Box II:11, Folder 1)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dispersal, 1990 October-1991 April (Box II:11, Folder 2)
    - The Greeks and the Sea (Small Gallery), 1990 October-1991 Febraury (Box II:11, Folder 3)
    - The Greeks and the Sea (Small Gallery), 1990 July-November (Box II:11, Folder 4)
    - Mabou Mines -- Shipping, 1985 August-1991 January (Box II:11, Folder 5)
    - Tom Wolf and Ken Chu (Small Gallery/WSW), 1990 October 26-November 15 (Box II:11, Folder 6)
    - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Correspondence, 1990 October-1991 May (Box II:11, Folder 7)
    - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Loans, 1991 January (Box II:11, Folder 8)
    - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Shipping, 1991 January-February (Box II:11, Folder 9)
    - Interrogating Identiry -- Loans, 1990 (Box II:11, Folder 10)
    - Interrogating Identiry -- Lenders, 1990 October-1992 March (Box II:11, Folder 11)
    - Interrogating Identiry -- Lenders (Rasheed Araeen), 1990 October (Box II:11, Folder 12)
    - Interrogating Identiry -- Lenders (Rebecca Belmore), 1991 March 5 (Box II:11, Folder 13)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Nadine Chan), 1991 January-October (Box II:11, Folder 14)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Albert Chong), 1991 April-1993 April (Box II:11, Folder 15)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Allan DeSouza), 1991 March-1992 April (Box II:11, Folder 16)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Jamelie Hassan), 1991 February-1992 April (Box II:11, Folder 17)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Mona Hatoum), 1990 November-1992 March (Box II:11, Folder 18)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Roshini Kempadoo), 1991 July-1993 April (Box II:11, Folder 19)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Glenn Ligon/Emily Fisher Landay), 1991 February-1992 March (Box II:11, Folder 20)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (MFA/Glenn Ligon), 1991 October-1993 August (Box II:11, Folder 21)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Whitfield Lovell), 1991 January-1993 April (Box II:11, Folder 22)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Lani Maestro), 1991 February-1993 June (Box II:11, Folder 23)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Lillian Mulero), 1991 January-1993 April (Box II:11, Folder 24)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Ming Mur-Ray), 1991 January-1993 May (Box II:11, Folder 25)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (San Diego Museum/Ming Mur-Rays), 1991 January-1993 March (Box II:11, Folder 26)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Keith Piper), 1991 January-1992 March (Box II:11, Folder 27)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Ingrid Pollard), 1990 April-1993 May (Box II:11, Folder 28)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Donald Rodney/Art Council Collection), 1991 January-1993 June (Box II:11, Folder 29)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Yinka Shonibare), 1990 October-1992 March (Box II:11, Folder 30)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Simmons/Janelle Reiring Metro Pictures), 1992 January-1993 April (Box II:11, Folder 31)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Lenders (Gary Simmons-Roy Boyd Gallery/Karin Bravin), 1990 December-1993 May (Box II:11, Folder 32)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Loan Extensions, 1991 May-1992 October (Box II:11, Folder 33)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Reception Plans, Circa 1989-1991 (Box II:11, Folder 34)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Travel Arrangements, 1991 (Box II:11, Folder 35)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Correspondence, 1988 May-1991 February (Box II:11, Folder 36)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Venue Schedule and Payment, Circa 1991-1992 (Box II:11, Folder 37)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Tour, 1991-1992 (Box II:11, Folder 38)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Duke University, 1992 August-1993 March (Box II:11, Folder 39)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Duke University, 1992 September (Box II:11, Folder 40)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Madison Art Center, 1991 December-1992 May (Box II:11, Folder 41)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Madison Art Center, 1991 April-June (Box II:11, Folder 42)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Center for Fine Arts, Miami, 1991 November-1992 August (Box II:11, Folder 43)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Center for Fine Arts, Miami, 1991 December-1992 May (Box II:11, Folder 44)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Miami Correspondence, 1991 March-1992 August (Box II:11, Folder 45)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Walker Correspondence, 1991 January-December (Box II:11, Folder 46)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Walker Art Center, 1991 May-1992 April (Box II:11, Folder 47)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Walker Art Center, 1991 April-November (Box II:11, Folder 48)
    - Interrogating Identity -- MFA Correspondence, 1990 October-1992 August (Box II:11, Folder 49)
    - Interrogating Identity -- MFA, Boston, 1991 April-1992 April (Box II:11, Folder 50)
    - Interrogating Identity -- MFA, Boston, 1991 April-September (Box II:11, Folder 51)
    - Interrogating Identity -- North Carolina Museum of Art, 1992 March-September (Box II:11, Folder 52)
    - Interrogating Identity -- North Carolina Museum of Art, 1992 April-May (Box II:11, Folder 53)
    - Interrogating Identity -- North Carolina (Contract), 1992 April-June (Box II:11, Folder 54)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Oberlin, 1992 June-1993 January (Box II:11, Folder 55)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Oberlin, 1991 July-1992 December (Box II:11, Folder 56)
    - Interrogating Identity -- Oberlin, 1991 July-1992 September (Box II:11, Folder 57)